I am NOT black mean that's what the world calls
me but it's not I didn't me come out of
my mother's womb saying hey everybody I'm black no I
was taught to be black and you were taught to
call me that along with whatever you call that along with whatever you call yourself
is just a label
see from birth the world force feeds us these labels
the world force feeds us these labels and eventually we
all swallow them and eventually we all swallow them digest
and accept the labels never ever digest and accept the labels never ever doubting
them but there's one problem doubting them but there's one problem labels
are not you and labels are not me just labels
but who we truly are is not skin deep see
when I Drive my car no one would ever confuse
the car for me well when I Drive my body
why did you confuse me for my body it's
get it not me let break it down so your
bodies are just cars that we your bodies are just cars that we operate
and drive around the dealership operate and drive around the dealership we
call society decided to label mine we call society decided to label mine the
black edition yours Irish or the black edition yours Irish or white
edition and with no money down white edition and with no money down zero
percent APR and no test drive we were forced to
own these cars for the rest of our lives forgive
me but I fail to see the logic or pride
in defining myself or judging pride in defining myself or judging another
by the cars we drive because who truly are is
found inside listen I'm not here to tell you how
science has concluded that genetically we're all concluded that genetically we're all mixed
in racing the human species mixed in racing the human species doesn't
exist or how every historian doesn't exist or how every historian knows
that race was invented in the 15th century to divide
people from each other century to divide people from each other and
it has worked perfectly no I'm not here to lecture
I just want to ask one
question who would you be if the world never gave
you a label never gave you a box to check
would you be white black Mexican check would you be white black Mexican Asian
Native American middle eastern Asian Native American middle eastern Indian
no we would be one will we together no longer
living in the error together no longer living in the error of
calling human beings black people or of calling human beings black people or white
these labels that will white people these labels that will forever
blind us from seeing a person forever blind us from seeing a person for
who they are but instead seeing them through the judgmental
prejudicial artificial filters of who we think they artificial filters of who we think they are
and when you let an artificial label define yourself then
my friend you have define yourself then my friend you have chosen
smallness over greatness and chosen smallness over greatness and minimize
your itself confined and minimize your itself confined and divided
your self from others and it is an undeniable fact
that where there is an undeniable fact that where there is division
will be conflict and division there will be conflict and
starts Wars therefore every war conflict starts Wars therefore every war has
started over labels it's always us has started over labels it's always us versus
them so the answer to war racism that sexism and
every other ism racism that sexism and every other ism is
so simple that every politician is misted it's the labels
we must rip them off isn't it funny how no
baby is born racist yet every baby cries when they
racist yet every baby cries when they hear the cries
of another no matter the gender culture or color improving
the gender culture or color improving the deep dad we
were meant to connect and care for each other that
is our mission and that is not my opinion that
is the truth in world that has sold us fiction
please listen labels only fiction please listen labels only distort
our vision that which is why distort our vision that which is why half
of those watching this will diss half of those watching this will diss or
feel resistance and conflicted but or feel resistance and conflicted but just
remember so did the caterpillar just remember so did the caterpillar before
it broke through its shell and before it broke through its shell and became
the Magnificent butterfly well these labels are our shells and
we must do the same thing so we can finally
spread our wings human beings were not spread our wings human beings were not meant
to be slapped with labels like meant to be slapped with labels like groceries
in supermarkets DNA cannot be groceries in supermarkets DNA cannot be regulated
by the FDA we were meant to be free and
only until we remove them all and stop living thinking
so small and stop living thinking so small will we
be free to see ourselves and each other for who
we truly are
so what can we do in the face of all
this madness and chaos what is the solution we can
love trying to control the mind is like trying to
flatten out water you just make more waves